export const data = [
    {
      question: 'What is the stream took by Bhavani?',
      option1: "Science",
      option2: "Commerce",
      option3: "Arts",
      option4: "Bi-PC",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the best student in our Tution?',
      option1: "Pardhu",
      option2: "Visalaxshi",
      option3: "Sruthi",
      option4: "Jasmin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
      option1: "Modem",
      option2: "Router",
      option3: "LAN Cable",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Your Tution sir favourit color?',
      option1: "Red",
      option2: "Green",
      option3: "Black",
      option4: "White",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
      option1: "Asia",
      option2: "Europe",
      option3: "North America",
      option4: "Africa",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: 'Favourite evening snacks of Sruthi',
      option1: "Roll",
      option2: "Chomin",
      option3: "Pani Poori",
      option4: "Chicken Momos",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
      option1: "Spam",
      option2: "Fake",
      option3: "Archived",
      option4: "Bin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
      option1: "Application Software",
      option2: "Internet",
      option3: "Operating System",
      option4: "Mouse",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: 'In which class Jashmin is studing?',
      option1: "10th",
      option2: "Degree 1st year",
      option3: "+2",
      option4: "+1",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
      option1: "Index Page",
      option2: "Homepage",
      option3: "Sitemap",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 2,
    },
  ];